玛吉:嗨,宝贝.
Maggie: Hi honey.
杰森:哦,你回来了…看到我的信用卡了吗?
Jason: Oh you're back...have you seen my credit cards?
玛吉:哦,是的…知道吗?打个电话,你就能获得加倍的信用金额.
Maggie: Oh yes...Did you know that you could double a spending limit with just one call?
杰森:开玩笑!你没打吧?
Jason: You're kidding!You didn't.
玛吉:放松点;我们要买的不过是开学促销产品.
Maggie: Relax; we only shopped at the back to school sales.
本:我马上就该上10年级了.还要穿马文克莱恩牛仔裤吗?
Ben: I'm supposed to start the tenth grade in Marvin Kline jeans?
汤姆:这跟价格昂贵的牛仔裤没差什么.
Tom: They are just as good as the expensive ones.
本:我要跟马文克莱恩牛仔裤终生相伴吗?不要!
Ben: Nothing comes between me and my Marvins?Please!
克里西:看啊,爸爸,我买了一个新饭盒.
Chrissy: Look daddy, I got a new lunch box.
杰森:汉尼拔莱克特牌的?思福斯牌的不也很好吗?
Jason: Hannibal lector?What happen to the surfs?
克里西:爸,我都上幼儿园了…我是大人了.
Chrissy: Dad, I'm starting kindergarden... I'ts a very fast crowd.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
开萝尔:我在装行李呢,周一我要搬到学校宿舍去住.
Carol: Well I have to start packing, I'm moving to the dorm on Monday.
本:好啊,好啊,好啊!!!
Ben: Yes, yes yes!!!
克里西:开萝尔,没有你,我们家就会变样了.
Chrissy: Carol, this house won't be the same without you.
本:没错,没错,没错!!!
Ben: Yes Yes Yes!!!
迈克:马文克莱恩?哈哈哈.
Mike: Marvin Klines?Hahaha.
杰森:嗨,迈克,很高兴你在这里.
Jason: Hey Mike I'm glad you're here.
听着,去学校报到之前,咱俩得谈谈.
Listen you and I have to have a little talk before we register for school.
迈克:哦,爸爸,
Mike: Oh I already did it dad...
我已经报到了…你们大家放宽心吧,这次我要好好学习了.
and you guys can rest easy, I'm taking my courses seriously this time.
玛吉:想学兔子巴格斯,来段即兴演出吗?
Maggie: Bugs bunny as archetype?Hero or Wascal?
迈克:如果伯里顿州立师范学院开这门课的话,
Mike: If Boynton state teachers college offers it, that's e..eee..eee.
那正好适…适…适…适…适合我.
e..enough for me.
杰森:够了.你今年要念哪些课程…心理学?你要选修心理学吗?
Jason: Come on What's with these courses this year...Psychology?You're taking psychology
迈克:是的,因为你是我的偶像,爸爸.
Mike: Yeah it's because I admire you dad.
本:哦,老天,这太肉麻了.
Ben: Oh man, is it getting thick in here or what...
玛吉:好啦各位,把各自的衣服收拾一下.
Maggie: Come on guys let's put your clothes away
杰森:对了,
Jason: Well, I wish we had discussed this first...
我还要先跟你商量件事…社区中心的补习班要找个学生去教课.
See; the learning antic's down at
the community center needs a student-teacher
迈克:怎么了?
Mike: So?
杰森:我还以为你有兴趣呢.
Jason: I thought you might be interested.
迈克:为什么?
Mike: Why?
杰森:一星期可以挣100美元.
Jason: Well, for one it pays a hundred dollars a week.
迈克:一星期有100美元?
Mike: A hundred dollars a week huh?
杰森:对,而且能为那些需要帮助的孩子们贡献一臂之力,
Jason: Yeah and you also get the satisfaction out of giving a hand to
你会获得满足感的.
some kids who need help.
迈克:每星期100美元吗?不,爸爸,不行…学习太紧,我脱不开身的.
Mike: A hundred dollars a week huh?No, dad I can't...I'm going to be busy with school.
杰森:伯里顿学院会为授课的学生增加学分的.
Jason: Boynton state offers course credit for student teaching
迈克:那好,我干.
Mike: Ok I'll do it.
杰森:你去吗?
Jason: You will?
迈克:是的.
Mike: Yeah.
杰森:那就好.
Jason: Yeah.
迈克:是很好.现在我可以放弃心理学了.杰森:不……
Mike: Yeah, all right now I can drop psychology.Jason: No
克里西:我不喜欢幼儿园怎么办呢?
Chrissy: What if I don't like kindergarden?
玛吉:哦,克里西,你今天肯定会很开心的…记得要有礼貌,要大方点,还要听老师的话.
Maggie: Oh Chrissy you are going to have so much fun today...Just remember to be polite and share, and do what your teacher says.
本:好主意,妈妈.你应该把这些教导刺到她额头上.
Ben: Great advice mom.Why don't you just tattoo "dweeb" on her forehead?
克里西:等一下.没人说要刺字啊.
Chrissy: Wait a minute.Nobody said anything about tattoos.
玛吉:宝贝,你哥哥只是打了个比方,
Maggie: Honey your brother is just using a figure of speech,
就是"牢牢记住"的意思.
as in "put a sock in it".
本:妈妈,在开学的第一天,
Ben: Mom, on the first day of school, if you are not careful,
一不小心你就会留下终生的遗憾.
you'll get a label that's going to dog you for the rest of your life.
克里西:怎么回事?
Chrissy: Like what?
本:坐前排,那是"小笨蛋".
Ben: Sit in front, "dorfburger" Answer any questions: Bugerhead;
回答任何问题:大头;跟带眼镜的人打交道:幼稚小孩;最重要的是:别吃绿果冻.就这些,
Hang out with anyone wearing glasses: Geekus Maximus; And most important:
回头见,小家伙.
Eat the green jello, asta la vista baby.
玛吉:吃绿果冻怎么了?
Maggie: What is wrong with green Jello?
本:被人嘲笑是"酸嘴普洛特尼克".
Ben: Leo lime tongue plotnic.
玛吉:他是谁啊?
Maggie: And who is he?
本:就是象棋俱乐部的秘书兼会计啊.
Ben: Just the secretary/ treasurer of the chess club.
克里西:哦,天啊…我就喜欢吃绿果冻.
Chrissy: Oh my gosh...I like green jello!
玛吉:别乱说,本…克里西,
Maggie: Cut it out Ben...
你想吃多少绿果冻都没关系的.
and Chrissy you just eat all the green jello you want.
本:那大家都会叫她"酸嘴"的!
Ben: There gonna call you lime tongue!
开萝尔:多么开心的一天啊!真是满心欢畅,
Carol: Isn't it a glorious day?
我要展翅高飞,什么东西都不带.
I feel intrepid, leaving the nest and taking nothing with me.
杰森:什么都不带?
Jason: Nothing uh?
迈克:开萝尔,我刚才不小心动了你的吉他.
Mike: Carol, I think I accidentally just tuned your guitar.
开萝尔:今天我心情很好.
Carol: I'm in such a good mood today that not even an annoying pest like
连你这样的讨厌鬼我都不介意.
you could bother me.
迈克:哦,说什么,开萝尔,讨厌鬼?
Mike: Oh please Carol, annoying?
开萝尔:迈克,没开玩笑,你还不如讨厌鬼呢…
Carol: Mike, I'm serious, not just annoying...
杰森:嗨,嗨,你们别闹了;今天是个特殊的日子…你们休战好吗?
Jason: Hey hey can we please maybe; it's a special day....How about a truce?
迈克,第一天去讲课,你紧张吗?
Mike, you got any butterflies about your first day teaching?
迈克:怎么会呢,爸爸.我全背地滚瓜烂熟."这是你们的课本,
Mike: Oh no way dad, I got all my lines memorized.
大家自习,下课".你觉得怎么样?
Heres your books, study on your own, class dismissed.What do you think?
开萝尔:切,人们可以把你拍成一部电影,就叫.
Carol: Jee, maybe they can make a movie about you.Drool, and deliver.
迈克:你好,打扰一下,你是弗兰西斯 泰德斯科吗?
Mike: Hello, uh excuse me, Francis Tedesco?
弗兰西斯:还没到8点呢.(叹气)需要帮忙吗?
Francis: Not until 8am.(Sigh) How may I serve you?
迈克:哦,我是来上补习班的.
Mike: Uh, well I'm here for the remedial studies class.
Francis: 8:30, seventh floor, room C.Whoom the teacher, go to jail
迈克:不是,你搞错了.我就是老师.
Mike: No you don't understand, you see, I'm the teacher.
弗兰西斯:你是西沃吗,迈克尔 西沃?
Francis: You're Seaver, Michael A?
迈克:在伯里顿学院他们都叫我"傻瓜老师".
Mike: Or as they call me at Boynton state "the teaching fool".
弗兰西斯:学生老师都这样,笑话连篇,
Francis: Student teachers full of jokes and youthful enthusiasm.
充满青春激情.
How long do you think it will be until your dreams are shattered?
你认为要过多久你的美梦会破灭?美梦破灭……
Your dreams broken...
迈克:我爸爸告诉我必须待到4点半.那是什么?
Mike: Well, my dad said I had to stay until 4:30.What are those?
弗兰西斯:西沃先生,这是我的工作…全是表格.HUD表格,HRA表格,
Francis: This Mr.Seaver is what I do...Forms.
HUD forms, HRA forms, ATW forms, I-9 forms, W-4 forms...I hate forms
可我必须一式三份的填好每一张.
And yet I must fill out everyone in triplicate
迈克:为什么?
Mike: Why?
弗兰西斯:只有这样才能消除杂乱无章的状态.
Francis: It's the only thing that stands between us and anarchy.
迈克:是的.我很钦佩你的责任心.
Mike: Yeah, I feel the same way about Brand.
弗兰西斯:西沃先生,我们先聊两句.
Francis: Mr.Seaver, let's interface for a moment.
你真想投身到这份工作中去吗?
Are you really committed to this job?
迈克:是的,我会尽心尽力的.
Mike: Yeah, pretty much I think.
弗兰西斯:这是聘用表格.比填写这些聘用表格更难受的是填写这些解聘表格.
Francis: These are your hiring forms.
The only thing more agonizing than filling these out is filling out these
termination forms.
前者就像用羊角榔头掀起你的鼻子.
This task is like having a claw hammer shoved up your nose.
后者就像把你的鼻子拨掉.
This one is like having it yanked out.
我们的要求就是在开始上课之前,你得保证坚持下去.
All I ask is that before you start working here you will agree to stay.
迈克:嗨,"傻瓜老师"不知道"辞职"两个字怎么写.
Mike: Hey the teaching fool does not know the meaning of the word quit.
弗兰西斯:你一周要来上两天课;每半个月对你进行考评.
Francis: You will be in charge of the students two days a week; you will be evaluated bi-monthly.
记住,这些补习学生需要额外的关注.
Remember these are remedial students that need extra attention,
这是你这个"傻瓜老师"应该做的.
which you- the teaching fool- will provide.
迈克:知道了,没问题.太棒了…我今天要教些什么呢?我擅长手工课.
Mike: Ok, all right, great...well what should I start teaching today? I'm great at arts and Crafts.
弗兰西斯:科学.
Francis: Science.
迈克:科学……我最好的几个朋友都是科学高手.
Mike: Science....Some of my best friends took science.
开萝尔:太棒了…现在这是一个独立女性的房子.
Carol: Perfect...now this is the room of an independent woman.
安 米勒:开萝尔 西沃?
Ann Miller: Carol Seaver?
开萝尔:玛丽 安 米勒?见到你太高兴了.
Carol: Marie Ann miller?I am so pleased to meet you.
我想说的是,我能住在这个宿舍里真是太兴奋了.
I just want to say I'm so excited about living in the dorm.
我相信我们熟悉以后会成为好朋友的.
I know we are going to become great friends as we grow to know each other.
安 米勒:你现在能去餐厅待一,两个小时吗?
Ann Miller: Do you have a couple of hours to spend in the cafeteria right now?
开萝尔:好的.
Carol: Yes.
安 米勒:好极了.我有个男朋友,我们希望单独待会.
Ann Miller: Great because I have a boyfriend and we would like to be alone.
Mike: Uh, hey everybody...Good morning...I'm your teacher.
My name is Mike seaver...S
e a v e r and we will be starting at the beginning today
第一章:引力.拼写是g r a v…i t y,gravity.呃,大家听好了…引力这玩意很简单,对吗?
Chapter 1: Gravity.That's g r a v... i t y, gravity.Uh, well, let's face it...this gravity stuff is pretty easy right?
要不然放在课本的开头干什么呢?懂吗?
I mean why else would they put it in front of the book?Ok?
我是说,
I mean, I could tell you about it,
我可以给你们讲解,但我不想侮辱你们的智力.
but I don't want to insult your intelligence.
这样吧,这节课我们还有59分钟.
All right so that leaves about 59 minutes to kill.
对了,那天晚上有谁看过"尼克斯"对"公牛"的比赛?
So anybody see the Knicks-Bulls game the other night?
卢克:西沃老师?西沃老师?打扰一下!!!今天这堂课讲的应该是引力.
Luke: Mr.Seaver?Mr.Seaver?Excuse me!!!I thought today's subject was gravity.
迈克:那好吧,
Mike: Ok fine, fine, fine...
好吧…我本来想给你们灌输点新鲜的东西,
I was just trying something a little new with you guys but I can see you
但看来你们还没做好准备呢.
are just not ready for it yet.
好吧,我们就照本宣科吧……你们开心了?引力是一种向…
Ok, we will go by the book....you happy?Gravity is the centr....
向…向心力.有了它,
Centp...centripetal force that keeps the earth from flying to pieces,
地球就不会被扯成碎片,宇宙就不会变成黑暗,无边和荒凉的尘埃和云彩.
and the universe from becoming a dark, endless, desolate cloud of dust.
哎呀,天啊…
Wow...Bumber...
卢克:西沃老师?用英语讲是什么意思啊?
Luke: Mr.Seaver?What does that mean in English?
迈克:问的好.
Mike: A fair question. A very fair question...
问的很好…谁能回答这个问题?
Does anybody have the answer to that?
好吧,
Well, before I give you my own personal explanation,
在我解释给你们听之前,
why don't we see what the so called expert's have to say...
我们还是来看看所谓的专家们是怎么说的吧…不论质量大小,
The earth's gravity exerts a constant and
地球引力对一切物体都施加不变而同等的力.例如,
equal force on all objects, regardless of mass,
一根羽毛和一枚硬币必定以完全相等的速度降落.
for example a feather and a coin must fall at exactly the same speed.
卢克:西沃老师?
Luke: Mr.Seaver?
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
卢克:你刚才说羽毛和硬币会以完全相等的速度降落.
Luke: You just said that a feather and a coin would fall at exactly the same speed.
迈克:我肯定没说…哦,我说过.
Mike: I certainly did not...oh I did.
卢克:但它们不会这样.我试过的.
Luke: But they don't.I tried it.
迈克:可课本是这样说的,那么我们为什么不继续往下讲呢?
Mike: Well the book says that they do, so why don't we just move on ok?
卢克:请证明一下.
Luke: Prove it.
所有学生:嗷…
Everybody: O...
迈克:好吧,好吧.羽毛,硬币.
Mike: Ok, ok fine.Feather, quarter.
卢克:课本错了.这是不争的事实.
Luke: The book is wrong, end of story.
迈克:他们在印刷前应该核对过的.好吧,好吧,我懂了.
Mike: They should check this stuff out before they printed it.Ok ok I got it.
卢克:怎么扔都一样.
Luke: It doesn't matter how you drop them.
你就算磨破嘴皮子结果都一样.
You can blow them out your ears if you want.
硬币肯定先着地.
The smarter money is on the quarter.
迈克:我办不到.这小子不知道他在说什么.
Mike: I don't get this.This guy doesn't know what he's talking about.
学生一:你也不知道.
Student 1: Neither do you.
学生二:结果,老师比我们这些学生还笨.
Student 2: Finally, a teacher that's dumber than we are.
这个国家是不是太伟大了?
Is this a great country or what?
玛吉:嗨,宝贝,幼儿园好不好?
Maggie: Hi honey, how was kindergarten?
克里西:我今天倒霉透顶了.
Chrissy: This was the worst day of my life
玛吉:怎么了?
Maggie: Oh what happened?
克里西:没什么,我坐在后面,
Chrissy: Nothing, I sat in the back, no one talked to me,
没人跟我说话,后来给小朋友们发乐器的时候,轮到我了是一根棍子.
and when they passed out the musical instruments, I got the stick.
玛吉:哦,宝贝,
Maggie: Oh honey everyone gets the...That happens to everyone sometimes.
每个人都会有倒霉的时候.对了,你照本说的那样去做了吗?
Wait a minute; did you do what Ben said?
克里西:我可不想当"大头".
Chrissy: I didn't want to be a "dorfburger".
玛吉:本·西沃,
Maggie: Ben Seaver, do you know what you did by filling your sister's
知不知道你把自己的愚蠢的想法灌到妹妹的脑袋里了……
head with your silly....
本:妈妈,等会再骂吧.我今天倒霉透顶了.
Ben: Mom can this wait?I just had the worst day of my life.
克里西:你也分到棍子了?
Chrissy: Did you get the stick too?
本:比这还糟.上历史课,我想坐到后排去.但不……所有的好座位都给占了.
Ben: Worse.In history, I tried to sit in the back, but noooo., all the good seats were taken.
克里西:你坐到前排了?
Chrissy: You sat in the front?
本:对啊.就在桑普森老师的眼皮底下,说实话,她的鼻子可真不怎么好看.
Ben: Yeah.Right under Mrs.Sampson's nose, which -believe me -is not a pretty site.
玛吉:哦,本…
Maggie: Oh Ben...
本:后来吃午饭的时候,几个留鬓角的大个家伙逼我吃绿果冻.
Ben: Then at lunch, some big guy with sideburns forced me to eat green jello.
上帝啊,我喜欢吃.
God help me, I liked it.
克里西:你吃绿果冻了?
Chrissy: You ate green jello?
本:是的.我好像成了可恶的磁铁.整个象棋俱乐部的人都围着我转.他们选我当了队长.
Ben: Yeah, and I was like the nerd magnet.The whole chess club sat with me.They elected me president.
玛吉:哦,本.看起来并不可恶嘛…
Maggie: Oh Ben, that doesn't make you a nerd...
本:不可恶?看看:学校的护士说我需要配眼镜了.这是我最讨厌的事了.我倒霉到家了.
Ben: No, well this does: The school nurse says I need glasses.We are talking
full frontal nerdity.I've hit rock bottom
克里西:还没呢.你小妹妹跟你患难与共.
Chrissy: Not yet.Your baby sister is going to beat you up.
玛吉:嗨,开萝尔,我没想到你回家来吃饭.
Maggie: Oh hi Carol, I wasn't expecting you home from dinner.
开萝尔:妈妈,我没心思理会你的想法.
Carol: Mom, I don't have time for your problems.
我今天倒霉透顶了.
I just had the worst day of my life.
玛吉:你宿舍好不好?
Maggie: How was your dorm room?
开萝尔:你为什么不去问问在那里待过的人.比方说我同屋的男友.
Carol: Why don't you ask somebody who spent some time there?Like my roommate's boyfriend
玛吉:(哈哈笑)
Maggie: (laughing)
开萝尔:妈妈,有那么好笑吗?
Carol: Mom, what's so funny?
玛吉:对啊,
Maggie: Well, a very similar thing happened to me while I was in college...
我上大学的时候也发生了这样的事…当时有个女孩也有个黏糊糊的男朋友.
There was this girl who had this stud boyfriend, they were always at it,
他们总是待在宿舍里如漆似胶.终于有一天,
they never stopped, until one day her roommate decided shed had enough,
她的室友忍无可忍,于是她气冲冲地进去把那个女孩彻底赶出去了.
and she marched right in there and she told her off for good.
开萝尔:你就是那个室友吗?
Carol: And you were the roommate?
玛吉:不是,我是有黏糊糊男友的那个女孩.
Maggie: No I was the girl with the stud boyfriend.
开萝尔:哦,妈妈.爸爸就是那个男友吗?你们总是待在一起?总是如漆似胶?
Carol: Whoa, mom.And dad was the stud?You two were always at it?You never stopped?
玛吉:不是,实际上,
Maggie: No, actually the stud was Danny Cross.
那个男孩是丹尼 克罗斯.
It was a little bit before I mentioned your father,
那发生在我认识你爸爸之前一点.我希望你就别再继续追问了…
so I'd appreciate it if you didn't mention it...
杰森:嗨,女士们.
Jason: Hi ladies.
玛吉:嗨.
Maggie: Hi.
杰森:追问什么?
Jason: Mention what?
开萝尔:哦,没什么,我们只是在谈论妈妈住宿舍时候的事.
Carol: Oh nothing we were just talking about mom's days in the dorm.
杰森:呵呵,丹尼 克罗斯那件事…
Jason: Hoho, the Danny cross thing...
玛吉:谁告诉你我和丹尼 克罗斯的事?
Maggie: Who told you about me and Danny Cross?
杰森:丹尼 克罗斯.要不我为什么把你支走呢?
Jason: Danny Cross.Why did you think I asked you out?
迈克:进来.
Mike: Come in.
杰森:嗨,你没下来吃饭,
Jason: Hey we missed you at dinner;
我以为也许你爱吃妈妈做的拿手的瑞典肉丸子.
I thought maybe you'd like some of your mom's famous Swedish meatballs.
迈克:哦,谢谢了,爸爸.我不饿.我今天一败涂地.
Mike: Ah, no thanks dad, I'm not hungry.It was a total failure.
杰森:怎么了?
Jason: What happened?
迈克:我讲课了.
Mike: I spoke.
杰森:哦,振作点,事情没那么糟糕吧.
Jason: Oh come on, it couldn't have been all that bad.
迈克:还没有?爸爸,
Mike: Oh no?Dad, I had an entire class laugh at me today.
今天全班的人都笑话我.
One kid said I was dumb.
一个孩子说我笨.他唯一证据就是另一个孩子说我蠢.
The only argument he got was from another kid that said I was stupid.
杰森:你真地认为讲课很容易吗?
Jason: Did you really think that teaching was going to be easy?
迈克:要不我为什么去啊?
Mike: Why do you think I signed up?
爸爸,我以为讲课就是让孩子们在课堂上做做练习,
Dad, I thought teaching was going to be all pop quizzes and looking up
然后再从课本后面找出答案来.
answers in the back of the book.
但是,一个滑头的小孩子不停地让我解释.
But there was this one smart little kid who kept asking me to explain stuff.
我是说,每当我不明就里的时候,
I mean every time I didn't know what I was talking about,
他就向我开火.
he would fire off another round.
他就是一个专门找茬的捣蛋鬼.我是说,他有什么毛病吧?我上学的时候从来不提问题.
He was like a dumb seeking missile.I mean what's with him?I didn't ask questions in school.
杰森:好了,迈克,总有比你聪明的孩子.这样的人才会推动你不断前进.
Jason: Well, there's always going to be one kid smarter than you Mike, that's the one that's going to keep you on your toes.
迈克:是啊,你就这么肯定?
Mike: Yeah, what makes you so sure?
杰森:当然了.因为我有个比我聪明的儿子.
Jason: I know, I got a son who's smarter than I am.
迈克:别谦虚了,爸爸,你比本强多了.
Mike: Oh come on dad, you got it all over Ben.
杰森:我说的是你,迈克.
Jason: I'm talking about you Mike.
好了,我很少对你这样说话.
Come on, I don't tell you all the time, but I got faith in you.
但我对你有信心.要知道讲课可不是讨价还价.
So teaching is a little more than you bargained for.
你要么坚持下去,要么半途而废.
You are either going to stick with it, or you are going to give it up.
我知道,你会做出正确的选择.
And I know you will know the right thing to do.
弗兰西斯:啊,西沃先生,
Francis: Ah Mr.Seaver, after arduous work,
经过繁杂的工作,我刚刚把你的聘用文件递交上去了.欢迎加入.
I have just sent your hiring package downtown.Welcome aboard.
迈克:泰德斯科先生,我得跟您谈谈.
Mike: Ah, Mr.Tedesco we have to talk.
弗兰西斯:谈什么?
Francis: About what?
迈克:我说了你会笑话我的…呃,你还记得昨天我们曾谈论过投身教学的事吗?
Mike: Well, you are going to laugh...you see uh, remember yesterday when we were talking about teaching and commitment?
弗兰西斯:你打退堂鼓了吗?
Francis: You're quitting.
迈克:请听我解释.昨天晚上,
Mike: Well, let me explain.
我爸爸说他知道我会做出正确的选择.
See, my dad told me last night that I would know the right thing to do
今天早上,我明白该怎么做了.
and, well, this morning it was perfectly clear.
泰德斯科先生,你怎么了?
Mr.Tedesco are you ok?
弗兰西斯:我左眼的后面一阵阵的剧痛.
Francis: I have a sharp blinding pain behind my left eye
迈克:那我该做些什么?
Mike: Well, can I get you something?
弗兰西斯:西沃!!!我们谈地好好的.
Francis: Seaver!!!We interfaced.
迈克:泰德斯科先生,我会尽全力弥补的.
Mike: Mr.Tedesco, I'll do anything to make it up for you.
弗兰西斯:那今天就去上课.
Francis: Teach your class today.
迈克:我会做别的事来弥补.
Mike: I'll do anything else to make it up for you.
弗兰西斯:西沃,眼下我根本没办法找到别的代课老师.你必须教,你会去教.
Francis: Seaver, I can't possibly get a replacement on such short notice.Teach you must and teach you will.
迈克:但是…
Mike: But...
弗兰西斯:你先去吧.
Francis: In a few moments,
等剧痛稍好点后,我就给你填解聘的表格.
when the blinding pain subsides I'll start work on your termination forms.
现在我想单独待一会.
Now I'd like to be alone.
迈克:哦,太抱歉了.我只是不好意思再面对那些孩子了.
Mike: Look, I'm sorry, it's just that I can't face those kids again.
弗兰西斯:我现在两眼直冒金星.如果不是疼痛造成的,
Francis: I'm seeing tiny white explosions.
这些金星一定很美.
Under different circumstances they might actually be pretty.
开萝尔:够了,你们两个.我忍受不了你们肮脏的行为了.这是我的房间,我也有权利待在这里.你出去.
Carol: All right you two, enough with this smut face.This is my room, I have rights too, and I want you out.
你听到了吗?出去!啊,
Did you hear me?Out!Hey you are not Mari Ann's boyfriend....
你不是玛丽 安的男朋友…你也不是玛丽 安.这不是我贴在墙上的招贴画.
and you aren't Mari Ann.And what happened to my posters?
天啊,我走错楼层了.再会.
Mercy, I'm on the wrong floor.Tata.
卢克:西沃老师?可以开始上课吗?
Luke: Mr.Seaver?Are we going to start?
迈克:哦,是的…好的,大家坐好.首先我们温习一下昨天…
Mike: Yes, yeah...ok everyone have a seat.Ok, now about yesterday...
每个学生:哦,天啊…
Everyone: Oh man.....
学生一:安静,大家安静…"爱因斯坦教授"要讲课了.
Student 1: Chill, chill everybody...Professor Einstein is talking.
学生二:你今天打算教我们点什么?是关于太阳好像真地,
Student 2: What are you going to teach us today?
真地很热吗?
The sun is like really really hot?
迈克:不,今天我们要继续探讨引力的问题.
Mike: No, today we are going to continue the discussion on gravity.
好了,我们要把这个问题搞懂,即使这要花一整天的时间.
Ok, now we are going to get this right, if it takes all day.
学生二:我最好数着日历本.
Student 2: I better clear my calendar.
迈克:听好了.不论质量大小,地球引力对一切物体都施加不变而同等的力.
Mike: Ok, the earth's gravity exerts a constant and equal force on all objects, regardless of mass.
比如,一根羽毛和一枚硬币必定以完全相等的速度降落.
For example, a feather and a coin, must fall at exactly the same speed.
一旦去掉空气阻力的因素…空气阻力!!!
Once the factor of air resistance is removed....
嗨!别动.那是一个水气球吗?
Air resistance!!!Hey!Hold it right there.Is that a water balloon?
学生:是的,老师.
Student: Yes, yes sir.
迈克:有创意.很好…谁还有这玩意?同学们,同学们,昨天我们没有考虑空气阻力的因素.
Mike: Good thinking.All right...has anybody else got one?Guys, guys, guys, yesterday we didn't account for the air resistance.
卢克:什么?
Luke: What?
迈克:好,大家跟我来.我们来把气球扔到窗外去.好,大家看好了:一个重气球,一个轻气球.
Mike: Ok, everybody follow me.We are going to throw them out the window.Ok, everyone observe: A heavy balloon, and a light balloon.
好,卢克,你来计算时间.
Ok, Luke, I want you to time this.
卢克:2点2秒.
Luke: 2.2 seconds.
学生:两个气球同时掉到猫身上…
Student: That cold cocked that cat at the same time...
迈克:那好,这说明什么?
Mike: Ok, now what does that mean?
卢克:说明猫被打晕了?
Luke: The cat is unconscious?
迈克:不,
Mike: No, it means that whatever we drop will take 2.2 seconds to hit
这说明不论我们扔什么都会花2点2秒时间达到地面.
the ground.
卢克:我们还扔什么?
Luke: What else can we drop?
学生:新年帽子.
Student: New year's hat.
卢克:还是2点2秒.我们扔大一点的东西…
Luke: 2.2 seconds, let's try something bigger...
学生三:对了,特德的午饭.
Student 3: Yeah, T.D's lunch.
学生二:嘿,那是我妈妈做的!!!
Student 2: Hey my mom packed that!!!
卢克:2点2秒.
Luke: 2.2 seconds.
学生一:我们也做了一个漂亮的实验.
Student 1: We made a pretty cool design too.
卢克:但羽毛就不会那么快地落下去.
Luke: But there's no way feathers are going to drop that fast...
迈克:但羽毛的问题在于空气阻力.
Mike: But the problem with the feather is that air resistance.
好了,也许课本里就有答案…我们继续实验.
Ok, now, maybe the book has more to say...ok come on.
卢克:这里有个真空管,跟图上的一样.
Luke: There's a picture in there of a tube, just like this one.
迈克:好…好了…可以了.硬币,羽毛,没有空气.
Mike: Ok...allright...here we go.Coin, feather, no air.
我们要展示真理.屏住呼吸,注意观察.成功了!!!
Moment of truth, watch and be amazed.It worked!!!
卢克:太棒了,再做一次!
Luke: That was great, do that again!
迈克:好,好的.
Mike: Ok ok.
卢克:这太神奇了,
Luke: This is amazing, this is incredible...
太不可思议了…你不像大家说的那么笨啊.
you're not as stupid as everyone says you are.
迈克:我不笨,我不笨.
Mike: I'm not, I'm not.
卢克:我们要像这样学更多的知识.
Luke: Hey we got to do more stuff like this.
迈克:你说对了.我们有整本书要学呢,
Mike: Oh yeah you bet, we got a whole book to go through here,
而我们才学到了…第几页?
and we are only on page what...?
卢克:第一页.
Luke: One.
迈克:那好,下面…下面…哦,我得跟泰德斯科先生谈谈去…呃,继续上课.泰德斯科先生!!!
Mike: Ok, now next time...next time...I got to talk to Tedesco...Uh, carry
on.Mr.Tedesco
弗兰西斯:啊,西沃先生,我刚刚把你的解聘书给寄出去.你解脱了.
Francis: Ah Mr.Seaver I just mailed in your termination packet downtown, you are free
迈克:泰德斯科先生,我们得谈谈.
Mike: Mr.Tedesco we have to talk.
弗兰西斯:谈什么?
Francis: About what?
迈克:我说了你会笑话我的,但"傻瓜老师"要坚持教下去了.
学生一:2点2秒!
00:22:11,800
Mike: Well, you're going to laugh, but the teaching fool is here to stay. Student 1: 2.2 seconds!